T-shirt Loewenling
Today I will introduce the T-shirt Loewenling
First, we have the T-shirt on
Place the Loewenling on the right spot
After opening the arrangement point, we put Rowan 0 on a suitable arrangement point.
Because it ends on the back side, so we arrange it on the other side of the arrangement point.
Then adjust its arrangement position, the distance between the arrow and the X.
After adjusting, we sew.
For sewing, we can use our free sewing 1 to N.
First sew our Rowan 1, then press the Shift key.
Then sew this circle of our circle.
Start sewing from this point on the back side.
After sewing, we sew the sewing line on both sides of our Rowan.
After sewing, we can simulate and press the control key.
After simulation, we switch our tool to the adjustment panel.
After selecting our panel, right-click to print.
After printing, simulate.
After simulation, turn off the simulation.
Then we need to create a fold line.
Use our tool to select the top and bottom two sides and create this line in the middle.
Show our inner line.
Then use the fold arrangement tool to select our inner line.
Then use this positioning ball.
Use the tip of the tool to fold.
When we fold, we turn around to see if we don't need to turn over.
We don't want our grid to be folded.
Then set the fold angle of our fold to zero.
Then sew the top and bottom two lines.
The sewing line type is changed to Turn.
This step is very important.
Then simulate.
After simulation, adjust the panel tool.
Select our panel.
Untie it.
Then simulate again.
Then apply the fabric of the pattern to the panel.
Find the fabric of the pattern in the window.
Select the panel.
Apply it.
OK.
In this way, we are done.
We can improve the quality of this clothing.
We can also fill in the color of the pattern.
Then simulate.
OK.
After simulation, we stop the simulation.
Hide the model.
Let's take a look at our pattern circle.
Its fold line is a little uneven.
Then we can use our inner line tool to 1 mm.
Give it a grid detail.
Make our fold line more round.
OK.
This is the production of our T-shirt pattern circle.
We will follow the rule that the needle is exposed to hit each bend of the patternril.
So there we go.
It is confident.
To this volt.
To this width.
To this divide.
And set this value to 0.